Guide to the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Company Files, 1966-2009
  - Diebold, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Dillard’s Inc., 1994-1997 (3 Folders) (Box 95, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Disney (ABC)1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Dole Foods, 1973-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 95, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Dollar General, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Dominion Resources, 1994-2000 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Donaldson, 1993-1997 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Dow Chemical, 1968-2000 (11 Folders) (Box 95, Folder 9 to 29)
  - Dow Jones, 1982-1997 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Doyle Dane Bernbach, 1976-1983 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Dresser Industries, 1979-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 1 to 2)
  - DTE Energy, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Duke Energy, 1974-1983, 1998-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Dun & Bradstreet, 1984-2001 (3 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 6 to 8)
  - DuPont
    - 1969-1999, Undated (9 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 9 to 17)
    - 1987-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Dynalectron, 1986-1987, Undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1971-2000 (9 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 4 to 12)
  - Eaton, 1980-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 13 to 14)
  - Echlin, 1985-1994 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - El Paso Company, 1977-1983 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Electrospace, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Eli Lilly, 1968-2000 (3 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 18 to 20)
  - Emerson Electric Company, 1980-1984 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Emerson Electric Company, 1980-2000 (3 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Engelhard, 1980-1985 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Englehard Mineral, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Enron, 1991-2001 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Equitable Resources, 1976-1997 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - E-Systems, 1985-1994 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - ESCO, 1990-1993 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Esmark, 1973-1983 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Exelon, 2000-2001 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Eximbank, 1975, Undated (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Exxon, 1972-1999 (6 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 13 to 18)
  - Exxon Mobil, 1984, 1994-2002 (2 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 19 to 20)
  - Ford, 1973-1999 (8 Folders) (Box 37, Folder 1 to 8)
  - Foremost McKesson, 1976-1982 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Fortune Brands, 1975-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 37, Folder 10 to 11)
  - Foster Wheeler, 1987-1995 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - FPL, 1976-1996 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Freddie Mac, 1992-1999 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Freeport-McMoran, 1995-1997 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Fry, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Fruit of the Loom, 1992-1999 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Gannett, 1990-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Gap, 1995-1999 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Gateway, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Geico, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gencorp, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - General Dynamics, 1979-2001, (13 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 1 to 13)
  - General Electric (GE)
    - 1972-2000, (18 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 1 to 18)
    - 1974-2000, (12 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 10 to 21)
  - General Mills, 1978-1998, (3 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 14 to 16)
  - General Motors (GM)
    - 1970-2000, (14 Folders) (Box 6, Folder 1 to 14)
    - 1972-1997, (5 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 17 to 21)
  - Georgia Pacific, 1972-1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - General Signal, 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - General Telephone & Electronics (GTE)
    - 1981-1997, (7 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 1 to 7)
    - 1974-1999, (3 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 1 to 3)
  - General Tire, 1976-1982 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Gerber, 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Gillette, 1976-2005, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 8 to 9)
  - Goodrich, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Goodyear, 1974-1996, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 11 to 12)
  - Great Lake Chemical, 1992-1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Grumman, 1977-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 11 to 12)
  - Gulf & Western, 1973-1989, (3 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 13 to 15)
  - Halliburton, 1978-2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Harnischfeger, 1992-1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Hartford, 1992-2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Hasbro, 1991-1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - H.B. Fuller, 1977-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - HCA, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Heinz, 1976-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Hewlett Packard, 1980-2000, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Hilton, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Home Depot, 1994-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 7 to 9)
  - Honeywell / Allied Signal
    - 1971-1996, (5 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 10 to 14)
    - 1971-2005, (9 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 1 to 9)
  - Hormel Foods, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Houston Industries, 1981-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 11 to 12)
  - Houghton Mifflin, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Household International, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Hubbell, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Hughes, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Humana, 1989-1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - IBM
    - 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 1976-2001, (11 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 1 to 11)
  - Illinois Tool, 1991-2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Ingersoll Rand, 1972-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Intel, 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Interface, 1991-1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Interfaith Alliance, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - International Basic, 1968-1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - International Flavors & Fragrances (IFF), 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - International Harvester, 1974-1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - International House of Pancakes (IHOP), 1982-1998 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - International Paper, 1973-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - International Telephone & Telegraph (ITT)
    - 1973-1996, (5 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 6 to 10)
    - 1977-1997, (3 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 16 to 18)
  - Interpublic Group, 1988-2000 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - James River, 1990-1997 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - JC Penney, 1972-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 45, Folder 8 to 9)
  - Jewel Companies, 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Johnson & Johnson, 1971-2000 (4 Folders) (Box 45, Folder 11 to 14)
  - Johnson Controls, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - JP Morgan, 1971-2000 (5 Folders) (Box 45, Folder 16 to 20)
  - JC Penney, 1985-2000 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Joy Technologies, 1988-1994 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - J.P. Stevens, 1976-1983 (3 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Kaiser, 1972-1980 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Kansas Gas & Electric Company, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Kellwood, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Kellogg’s, 1980-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 46, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Kemper, 1990-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Kenna Metal, 1990-1995 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Kennecott, 1969-1982 (3 Folders) (Box 46, Folder 9 to 11)
  - Kerr-McGee, 1971-1995 (4 Folders) (Box 46, Folder 12 to 15)
  - Key Corporation, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Kimberly-Clark, 1978-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 43, Folder 3 to 4)
  - King World, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Kmart/Sears, 1976, 1980-2001 (3 Folders) (Box 43, Folder 6 to 8)
  - Knight Ridder, 1989-2000 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Kohl’s, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Kraft, 1975-1988 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Kroger, 1976-2000 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Lands’ End, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Legent, 1990-1994 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Leggett & Platt, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Lilco, 1978-1983 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Limited, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Lin Broadcasting, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Lincoln National, 1978-2001 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Litton Industries, 1975-1995 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Liz Claiborne, 1995-1998 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Lockheed Martin, 1975-2005 (6 Folders) (Box 44, Folder 1 to 6)
  - Loews, 1988-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 44, Folder 7 to 8)
  - Long’s Drugstores, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Loral, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Louisiana Pacific, 1990-1997 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - LTV-Wilson, 1977-1980 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Lubrizol, 1989-1994 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Lucent Technologies, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - MacMillan, 1988-1993 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Macy’s, 1980-1986 (2 Folders) (Box 38, Folder 2 to 3)
  - Madison Gas & Electric, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Marriott, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Mars, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Marsh & McLennan 1987-1997 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Marshall & Isley, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Mattel 1978-1999 (2 Folders) (Box 38, Folder 9 to 10)
  - Maxus Energy, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Maxxam, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - May Stores, 1989-2001 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Maytag, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - MBNA, 1998-2001 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - MCA, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - McCann Erikson, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - McCormick, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - McDermott International, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - McDonalds, 1976-1999 (4 Folders) (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - McDonnell Douglass 1979-1981 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - McDonnell Douglas, 1976-1997 (4 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 1 to 4)
  - McGraw Hill, 1996-1997 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - MCI, 1990-1997 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Mead, 1988-2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Medtronic, 1988-1993 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Mellon Bank, 1994-1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Merck, 1970-2003 (6 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 10 to 15)
  - Merrill Lynch
    - 1971-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 16 to 17)
    - 1971-2006 (2 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Microsoft, 1988-2000 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Minnesota Mining, 1977-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Mobil, 1971-1998 (6 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 6 to 11)
  - Monsanto
    - 1969-1991 (2 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 12 to 13)
    - 1977-1999 (2 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 3 to 4)
  - Morgan Stanley, 1995-2000 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Morrison-Knudsen, 1991-1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Morton International, 1989-1997 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Morton Thiokol, 1986-1988 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Motorola, 1974-1998 (5 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 9 to 13)
  - Mylan Labs, 1994-1997 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Nalco Chemical, 1975-1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - National City, 1980-1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - National Semiconductors, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - National Steel, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Nations Bank, 1993-1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - NCNB, 1982-1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Nestlé’s, 1976-1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - New York Times, 1988-1996 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Nextel, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Newmont Mining, 1969-1995, (3 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 2 to 4)
  - Niagara Mohawk, 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Nike, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NL Industries, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Nordstrom, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk Southern, 1990-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Northeast Utilities, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Northern States Power, 1976-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Northern Telecom, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Northrop Grumman, 1975-1999, (3 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 13 to 15)
  - Northwest Airlines, 1984-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Northwest Gas, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Norton Company, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Norwest Corp, 1992-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Nucor, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NWNL, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Nynex, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Occidental Petro
    - 1974-1999, (6 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 1 to 6)
    - 1979-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - OEC Medical Systems, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Office Depot, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Oklahoma Gas & Electric, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Old Kent, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Olin, 1976-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 9 to 10)
  - Oregon Steel, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Oryx, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Oshkosh, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pacific Gas & Electric, 1974-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 14 to 15)
  - Pacific Telesis, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Pan American, 1971, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Parker Hannifin, 1986-1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Paramount, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Peabody Coal, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Peco, 1978-2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Penn Virginia, 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Power and Light Company, 1971-1994 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Pepsico
    - 1978-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 22 to 24)
    - 1990-2007 (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 3 to 4)
  - Perkin-Elmer, 1981-1986 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Pet Inc., 1978 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Pfizer, 1981-2001 (7 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 20 to 26)
  - Phelps Dodge, 1976-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 5 to 6)
  - Phibro, 1979-1986 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia Electric, 1977-1995 (3 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 27 to 29)
  - Philip Morris, 1971-2001 (7 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 30 to 36)
  - Phillips Petro, 1974-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Phillips Van Heusen, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Pier1 Imports, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Pillsbury, 1974-1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Pitney Bowes, 1971-1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Pioneer, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Pittston, 1976-1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - PNC Bank, 1978-1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Polaroid, 1971-2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Potlatch Corporation, 1984-1985, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Potomac Electric Power, 1976-1989 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - PP&L, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - PPG, 1983-2001 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Premark, 1987-1997 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Proctor & Gamble, 1975-2000, (2 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 16 to 17)
  - Providian Bancorp, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - PSE&G, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Quaker Oats, 1973-1996 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Ralston Purina, 1977-2000 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Raytheon, circa 1971-2002 (4 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 9 to 12)
  - Reader’s Digest, 1993-1998 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Reebok, 1993-1998 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Republic New York Corporation, 1979-1984 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Reuters, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1994-1998 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Rite Aid, 1983-2000 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - RJR Nabisco, 1975-1999 (4 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 4 to 7)
  - Rockwell Industries
    - 1975-1997 (7 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 1 to 7)
    - 1981-1995 (6 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 8 to 13)
  - Rollins, 1993, Undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Rosario Mining, 1976-1980 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - R.R. Donnelley, 1989-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 16 to 17)
  - Rubbermaid, 1985-1998 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Safeco, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Safety-Kleen, 1991-1997 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Safeway, 1978-2000 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - SallieMae, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Santa Fe Energy, 1993-1997 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Santa Fe International, 1997-1998 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Santa Fe Southern Pacific, 1976-1995 (2 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Sara Lee, 1986-2000 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - SBC, 1992-1997 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Schering-Plough, 1977-2000 (3 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 20 to 22)
  - Saks, 1998-2001 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Salomon, 1987-1996 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Schering-Plough, 1979-1997 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Schlumberger, 1978-1998 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Scientific Atlantic, 1991-992 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Scott, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Searle, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Sears/Kmart, 1977-2001 (2 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Security Pacific, 1980-1998 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Shell Oil, 1975-1986 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Shoney, 1993-1997 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Singer, 1983-1986 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Smithkline, 1982-19898 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Smucker’s, 1993-1997 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Sonoco/Sunoco, 1990-1997 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Southeast Bank, 1986-1994 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Southern, 1975-2000 (4 Folders) (Box 68, Folder 10 to 13)
  - Southern California Edison, 1979-1994 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Southwest Airlines, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Southwestern Bell, 1989-1995 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Sprint, 1994-1999 (2 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 7 to 8)
  - Square D, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Squibb, 1971-1989 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Standard Oil, 1972-1994 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Stanley Works, 1988, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Stone Container, 1992-1997 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Sun Microsystems, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Sun Trust, 1992-2000 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Sundstrand, 1987-1996 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - T. Rowe Price, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Tandy, 1986-1997 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Target Dayton Hudson, 1971-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 2 to 3)
  - Tecumseh, 1993-1997 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Tektronix, 1986-1993 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Teledyne, 1986-1992 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Teleflex, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Temple-Inland, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Tenneco, 1970-1996 (5 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 9 to 13)
  - Texaco
    - 1973-1997 (4 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 14 to 17)
    - 1976-1983 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - 1993-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Texas Instruments, 1982-1996 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Texas Utilities, 1970-1998 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Textron, 1978-2001 (4 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 3 to 6)
  - Thermo Electron, 1992-1998 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Thiokol, 1989-1997 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Time Warner, 1978-1998 (4 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 10 to 13)
  - Timken, 1986-1997 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Tokheim, 1987-1996 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Tosco, 1997-1999 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Toys “R” Us, 1990-1997 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Travelers, 1987-1998 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Tribune, 1990-1996 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Tricon, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - TRW, 1974-2000 (3 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 20 to 22)
  - Tyson, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - UAL, 1985-1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - UNC, 1977-1984 (3 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 2 to 4)
  - Unilever, circa 1975-1987 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Union Camp, 1977-1998 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Union Carbide, 1971-1997, Undated (9 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Union Electric, 1977-1997 (3 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Unicom, 1998-2000 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Union Electric, 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Union Pacific, 1977-2000 (3 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 3 to 5)
  - Uniroyal, 1971, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Unisys, 1971-1997 (3 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 7 to 9)
  - United Brands, 1978-1986 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - United Technologies, 1976-2000 (5 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 2 to 6)
  - Unocal, 1981-2001 (3 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 7 to 9)
  - Upjohn, 1979-1997 (3 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 10 to 12)
  - US Air, 1992-1997 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - US West, 1995-1997 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - USX, 1977-1997 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - United States Steel, 1974-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 1 to 2)
  - United States Surgical, 1986-1998 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - United Technologies, 1983-1999 (3 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 12 to 14)
  - US Healthcare, 1995-2005 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - UST, 1991-2000 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - VF, 1987-1997 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Viacom, 1997-2004 (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 5 to 6)
  - Vulcan, 1992-1994 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Wachovia, 1995-1997 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Wal-Mart, 1987-2005 (9 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 1 to 9)
  - Walgreen, 1993-1998 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Walt Disney, 1987-1997 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Walt Disney (ABC), 1987-2000 (3 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 11 to 13)
  - Warner-Lambert (1991-1997 (3 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 10 to 12)
  - Wells Fargo, 1975-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 13 to 14)
  - Wendy’s, 1987-1997 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Western Airlines, 1981-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Westinghouse, 1971-1997 (9 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 3 to 11)
  - Westvaco, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Weyerhaeuser, 1973-2000 (4 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 13 to 16)
  - Wheelabrator, 1992-1997 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Whirlpool, 1990-2000 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Whole Foods, 2005-2006 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin Power and Light, 1979-1980 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Witco, 1995-1996 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - WMX, 1984-1994 (2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 16 to 17)
  - Woolworth, 1983-1998 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Worldcom, 1999-2000 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - W.R. Grace
    - 1975-1997, (4 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 5 to 8)
    - 1986-1997 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Wrigley, 1993-1996 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Wright, 1971-1973 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - W.W. Grainger, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Wyeth (American Home Products), 1974-1997 (6 Folders) (Box 86, Folder 11 to 16)
  - Wynn’s, 1989-1997 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Xerox, 1974-1997 (5 Folders) (Box 86, Folder 18 to 22)
  - Zenith, 1991-1997 (Box 86, Folder 23)
- Series VI. U.S. Security and Exchanges Commission (SEC) Files, 1972-2007 [Bulk Dates: 1990-2004]
  The SEC Files contain records related to ICCR’s interaction with the SEC on both SEC policy issues and ICCR’s own proxy resolutions.
  The files include records related to ICCR’s advocacy on SEC policies such as corporate disclosure, proxy rules, shareholder rights and resolutions, and vacancies on the SEC. These records include campaign materials, clippings, correspondence, legal materials, memos, questionnaires, and reports.
  The ICCR also worked with the SEC on issues related to proxy resolutions filed by ICCR’s member organizations. These files include records on proxy resolutions, including chronological files with lists and copies of resolutions, as well as responses and information on legal cases.
  Copies of the texts of shareholder resolutions filed each year by ICCR's faith-based investors are also published in the Proxy Resolutions Book, which can be found in Publications (Series VII).
  The files are arranged in two ways. The first set of files conists of general files that are filed chronologically. The second set of files were originally filed together in groups that are roughly chronological, and the current arrangement follows that filing method.
  - Chronological Files--General
    - SEC
      - 1972-1984 (1 Box) (Box 106)
      - 1985-1986 (3 Folders) (Box 90, Folder 1 to 3)
      - 1989-1993 (11 Folders) (Box 90, Folder 4 to 24)
      - 1994-1997 (15 Folders) (Box 89, Folder 1 to 15)
      - 1997-2000 (8 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 10 to 17)
    - Shareholder Resolution Rules, 1996-2007 (2 Folders) (Box 97, Folder 20 to 21)
  - Chronological Files--Grouped Files
    - 1975-1981
      - General, 1975-1981 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Accounting Procedures, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Board of Directors, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Corporate Disclosure, 1975-1977 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - SEC Hearings, “Shareholder Communications, Participation in Corporate Electoral Process, and Corporate Governance,” 1977 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - 1990-1993
      - ABC Case, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Articles, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - Bishop Browning’s Letter to Episcopalians, 1992 April (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - Brokers, Pension Funds, Foundations, circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Campaigns, 1991-1993 (2 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Congress--Letters--SEC, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Congressional Responses, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Contracts, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Cracker Barrel SEC Challenge, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 31)
      - Dupont/SEC Environment Case, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 32)
      - Fax--Newspaper Articles on SEC Issue, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - Fax Ready--Congressional List and Standard Letter, 1992 April (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Fried Letter, 1992 March 11 (Box 82, Folder 20)
        (Donald Fried)
      - Fried’s Speech, 1992 February (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - ICCR Board Member, circa 1992 (Box 82, Folder 30)
        (Memo on SEC Campaign)
      - ICCR Memos
        - Congressional Committees, 1992 April 15 (Box 82, Folder 11)
        - SEC Update, 1992 May (Box 82, Folder 12)
        - SEC Alert, 1992 April (Box 82, Folder 13)
        - ICCR Members & Board, 1992 April (Box 82, Folder 14)
        - Governing Board, 1992 March 3 (Box 82, Folder 15)
        - Plan of Action, 1992 February 13 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - IRRC Corporate Governance Highlights--Executive Summary on SEC’s Decisions on Shareholder Communication and Corporate Executive Compensation Disclosure, 1992 June (Box 82, Folder 27)